<thread><orig_poster>stever</orig_poster><posted_at_date>November  4, 2014  7:22PM</posted_at_date><posted_at_datetime>2014-07-01T14:44:03+00:00</posted_at_datetime><views>6K</views><replies>96</replies><lastposted_date>July  1, 2014  2:44PM</lastposted_date><lasposted_datetime>2014-11-04T19:22:35+00:00</lasposted_datetime><tags>Acura, Acura MDX, 2015</tags><posts><username>stever</username><date>July  1, 2014  2:44PM</date><body>   
               Welcome to Edmunds discussion dedicated to 2015 Acura MDX leasing questions. Here you can find and discuss all the latest lease details for the 2015 MDX, including cap costs, money factors, residual values, acquisition fees, etc. Please post any leasing questions you have or any details you&#8217;d like to share about your own lease deals.

You can also research local dealer inventory and pricing, reviews, features, and specifications, on our  page.

To see all forums discussions about the MDX, including earlier model years, please visit our list of  discussions.

Navigation tips: To see the most recent information and activity, make sure to visit the latest post, which may be a few pages ahead. Click the pages numbers just below to go to a new page in the discussion -- or search the entire discussion by clicking the magnifying glass icon and entering keywords.

We also invite you to share your new car impressions on Edmunds  page.
            </body><username>chuckjr</username><date>June 18, 2014  7:10AM</date><body>
               FYI the 2015 MDXs are on some lots (maybe only one in LA) as much as I had hoped they would be motivated to start unloading 2014s their offer wasn't impressive. 
base SP $40,400 =  $545 pre-tax w $1500 drive off - 12k 36 mos

I told them no thanks and of course they started calling and emailing. Sale manager said that 2015s will be leased at or close to MSRP until there is support from acura in a few months.
            </body><username>4apex</username><date>July  1, 2014 12:17PM</date><body>
               I've been negotiating on a 2014 MDX FWD Tech but the monthly payment has been a bit high.  I was hoping that the money factor would drop this July 7th but dealer said not to hold my breath as they have very few MDXs on the lot.  SO he came back with a lease figure on a 2015 MDX FWD Tech that was a little better than what they were offering on the '14.  He told me that even though the money factor on the '15 was a bit higher (the workup showed the MF at .00170) BUT he said that the  residual was 4% higher (61%), so the higher residual resulted in a slightly lower payment on a '15.  By the way, this was on a 15k lease.

I've searched the Edmunds forums and can't find a "2015 Acura MDX Lease Questions", so can the moderator provide the current Money factor and residual for an MDX Tech and MDX Tech+Entertainment at 15k miles?  I understand that the MF and residual are the same for the AWD and FWD, correct?

Thanks!
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>July  1, 2014 10:49PM</date><body>
               

2014 numbers haven't changed, yet... Maybe, on July 8th..

2015 numbers are indeed .00170 MF and 61% for Tech and 60% for Tech/Ent. for 36mo, 15K/yr.    And, they are the same for both FWD and AWD
            </body><username>kenoberry</username><date>July  8, 2014 10:29PM</date><body>
               Assuming they'll change after the promotion that expired 7/7, I'm looking for revised numbers for 2014 MDX AWD + Tech for 36 mo, 15k. Same for 2015. Thanks!            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>July  8, 2014 10:56PM</date><body>
               

2014:  .00103 MF and 55% residual

2015:   .00164 MF and 61% residual.
            </body><username>kenoberry</username><date>July  9, 2014 12:45AM</date><body>
               Thanks, kyfdx
            </body><username>jessesj</username><date>July  9, 2014  7:59PM</date><body>
               kyfdx, would you please provide residuals for 2014/2015 MDX FWD + Tech for 36 mos./15k miles?  Thanks in advance.
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>July  9, 2014 11:02PM</date><body>
               

.00103 MF and 55% residual for 2014

.00164 MF and 61% residual for 2015
            </body><username>dinnyin</username><date>August  5, 2014 12:25AM</date><body>
               Any thoughts on how good the new July/August lease offers are?  Base only I think, but $0 down is only $550.            </body><username>agillman</username><date>August 16, 2014  4:41AM</date><body>
               Can you please provide residuals and money factors in California - 36 months/15,000 miles - for an MDX AWD with Tech.  Thank you!
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 16, 2014 12:59PM</date><body>
               

2015: .00164 MF and 61% residual.
            </body><username>pukimon311</username><date>August 16, 2014 11:17PM</date><body>
               Do you know if there's MF reduction for autopay with Acura? Because I am current Mercedes Benz owner too, I know MF reduction is available for autopay and MSDs.
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 17, 2014  1:59AM</date><body>
               

Not that I know of..
            </body><username>pukimon311</username><date>August 17, 2014  2:41AM</date><body>
               &#8204; - thank you
            </body><username>pr6147</username><date>August 21, 2014  6:27PM</date><body>
               I got a quote for Acura MDX AWD with Tech Package in SD.
Retail Price: 49,735
Sale Price: 47,488
Net Cap Cost: 48,282
Term: 36 months
Residual: 65%
Mileage: 10k
Monthly Payment: 580$

Is it good?
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 21, 2014  6:52PM</date><body>
               

Base MF is .00164 - with the rest of your numbers, I get a pre-tax payment of $575.37.

How is tax applied to a lease in SD?
            </body><username>pr6147</username><date>August 21, 2014  7:50PM</date><body>
               null
They gave me the exact number. Said my monthly payment will be 576-586.
I m new to this leasing so please let me know whether should I go ahead or look for alternatives            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 21, 2014  9:50PM</date><body>
               

Only you can decide if the deal is good enough to sign for. I don't make decisions with other people's money 
            </body><username>pr6147</username><date>August 21, 2014 10:11PM</date><body>
               

Thanks for the info
            </body><username>jddssc121</username><date>August 22, 2014  5:30AM</date><body>
               can you share #'s for an advanced package AWD 36/15?
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 22, 2014 12:57PM</date><body>
               

2015 MDX AWD Advance 36/15 - 59% and .00164
            </body><username>pr6147</username><date>August 22, 2014  1:38PM</date><body>
               can you please tell me the residual value and MF on 2015 acura mdx with tech and tech+entert pkg for 10k and 12k miles in SD and NE. Thanks  a lot
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 22, 2014  1:40PM</date><body>
               

.00164 MF and 63% for AWD with tech. Subtract 1% for Tech+Ent. Add 1% for 10K.
            </body><username>jddssc121</username><date>August 23, 2014  7:33PM</date><body>
               

thank you sir!
            </body><username>karhill1</username><date>August 24, 2014 12:55PM</date><body>
               Leases on the 2015 MDX are not very good at this time. The .00164 MF is about 3.9 percent.  That could result in additional monthly payments approaching $100 over a finance rate of .9 percent which Honda/Acura often uses to subvent their leases. Unless a lease is really necessary, probably better to wait a bit and see if Acura begins to subventions the MDX leases.

Leases are usually only a good bet when subvented by the OEM. This is one of the keys to a good lease.
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 24, 2014  1:39PM</date><body>
               

I would agree - lease numbers on brand new models (or a new model year) are not nearly as good as on the outgoing model or model year.

BMW seems to be the exception - the base MF for almost every model is .00130 for both 2014 and 2015.
            </body><username>tarheels71</username><date>August 27, 2014  1:48PM</date><body>
               Just picked up a '15 AWD with TECH for $551/month and $1315 down from Central NJ. Any comments on the numbers is appreciated. I worked a few dealers against one another for 3-4 days before settling at that. Thanks.
            </body><username>adii</username><date>August 28, 2014  2:57PM</date><body>
               tarheels71 which dealership you go to?
            </body><username>adii</username><date>August 28, 2014  2:57PM</date><body>
               

WHICH DEALER DID YOU GO THROUGH.
            </body><username>tarheels71</username><date>August 28, 2014  4:51PM</date><body>
               Ocean, NJ
            </body><username>tarheels71</username><date>August 28, 2014  4:51PM</date><body>
               

Ocean, NJ
            </body><username>tarheels71</username><date>August 29, 2014 12:24PM</date><body>
               

Good deal, bad deal, average deal?? Any ideas?
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 29, 2014  1:05PM</date><body>
               

Hard to say .... lease term, miles per year? What was the MSRP and selling price?
            </body><username>soapdish616</username><date>September  3, 2014 12:18AM</date><body>
               I would like to lease a 2015 Acura MDX SH-AWD w/ TECH package. MSRP is $49,735. What's the best deal I can get on this? Assume 36 months, 12k and 15k miles numbers ($0 down). Please be sure to share the sell price, money factor and residual value so I can double check the data the dealer gives me.

Can I get this for something like $540/month + tax? 0 down?
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September  3, 2014 11:16PM</date><body>
               

.00124 or .00154 MF, depending on region.  62%/60% residual for 12K/15K per year.
            </body><username>karhill1</username><date>September  4, 2014 12:02PM</date><body>
               I have been looking for a new MDX to replace my current MDX.  However, as Acura is not currently subventing leases on the 2015 MDX, this may not be the best time to lease an MDX.  Leases are always best when they are supported (subvented)  by the OEM with attractive money factors (MF).

Acura's current 2015 MDX MFs do not seem very appealing.  A MF of .00154 is over 3.5 percent.  This MF results in payments around $90 or more a month over a MF reflective of Honda/Acura's .9 percent financing.  Over a 36 month least period, that results in well over $3,000 in additional payments.

For such an amount, unless an exigency exits, it probably makes financial sense for many folks to postpone a lease of an MDX until the MF become more reasonable.
            </body><username>soapdish616</username><date>September  5, 2014  6:40PM</date><body>
               Was just offered: 2015 MDX AWD with Tech Package.

Lease: 36 months, 
Money Factor: .00124
MSRP: $49,735
Sell Price: $46,075
Residual: 60%

Payment with tax: $602. Nothing down.

I'm thinking this is bare bones price what I have gotten it down to.... I'm surprised that they are using .00124 money factor on 15k?? or is this a mistake by the sales guy?
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September  5, 2014 10:04PM</date><body>
               

60% RV for 36/15 with a MF of .00124.

$545.08 pre-tax with your numbers; $602 seems a bit high.
            </body><username>nj_mdx</username><date>September 10, 2014  3:00AM</date><body>
               Can you me the MF and RV for a 2015 MDX AWD w/Tech at 36 months and 10K miles/year in NJ?
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 10, 2014 11:11AM</date><body>
               

.00124 MF and 63% residual
            </body><username>khkillia</username><date>September 11, 2014  3:52AM</date><body>
               I am posting this on the 2014 and 2015 forum...sorry if that isn't the best way to get the information on my question.I got hosed on a BMW lease, which in turn made me really educate myself on lease's.That being said, I spoke with a Manager at an Acura Dealership and he stated that Acura doesn't do MSD's to lower the Money Factor, but they do a "One-Pay Lease" that really lowers the MF. Is anyone familiar with the One-Pay Lease, what the MF is, the pros and cons, does it change the residual on the vehicle?Thanks.            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 11, 2014 11:25AM</date><body>
                     
            </body><username>ozzynyc1</username><date>September 18, 2014  8:57PM</date><body>
               I was just offered 2015 MDX SH-AWD base, 10k, 36 months for $480 (that includes NY taxes) and $1378 out of pocket (plates, bank and first month). I don't know the selling price. Does this seem to be a good deal? Thanks.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September 18, 2014  9:33PM</date><body>
                     
Without knowing the MSRP and selling price, it's hard to fully evaluate your offer.            </body><username>ozzynyc1</username><date>September 19, 2014  1:05AM</date><body>
               Msrp is $45460. I don't have the selling price&#160;            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September 19, 2014  1:24PM</date><body>
                     
The dealer should be willing to provide that to you ....             </body><username>jpkreddy11</username><date>September 23, 2014  5:55PM</date><body>
               Please let me know the Residual and MF for the 2015 Acura MDX with Tech package in Michigan. I was offered a deal for 36/10k at $572/month and $833 at signing. The MSRP is 48840 (without destination) charges and selling price is 46530. Please let me know if this is a good deal.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September 23, 2014  7:22PM</date><body>
                     
.00124 MF and 63% for 36/10.With your MSRP and selling price, I get a pre-tax payment of $533.65/mo. 7-7.5% tax takes us to the $572/mo you were quoted.Seems a solid deal.            </body><username>fancylady</username><date>October  2, 2014 11:02PM</date><body>
               What are current money factor rates and residual for 2015 mdx tech/ent 36 mos/12k for PA?            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October  2, 2014 11:55PM</date><body>
                     
.00124 MF and 61% residual            </body><username>anguilla</username><date>October  6, 2014 12:41PM</date><body>
               Looking for a  2015 MDX AWD with Tech package.  36 month lease with 15k/year.There are a few dealers in nearby states that have good discounts off of MSRP.  What is the money factor and residual in each of these states for October and how long are these rates typically valid for?NJMDVAPANY            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October  6, 2014  1:19PM</date><body>
                     
60% is the residual for 36/15 on the MDX AWD with Tech.MF is .00124 for NJ, PA and NYMF is .00154 for MD and VAThese numbers are valid until 11/3/14.            </body><username>shankly</username><date>October  8, 2014  8:05AM</date><body>
               Curious if the lease terms on the 2015 MDX will improve or worsen after current promotion term ends on 11/3?Thanks in advance.&#160;            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October  8, 2014 11:25AM</date><body>
                     
.00154 MF and 61% residual.    The other region (which doesn't include Texas) has a .00124 MFAny ideas about what might happen next month is just a guess.   But, generally, deals get a little better towards the end of the calendar year.   I don't think the lease program would get worse, but again, just guessing.            </body><username>tjlions</username><date>October  9, 2014  1:42PM</date><body>
               2015 MDX, AWD w/tech,  36/15.  What is rv and mf in NC?  Thanks in advance.              </body><username>tjlions</username><date>October  9, 2014  1:43PM</date><body>
               Also, any idea what rate would be with a one payment up front deal?            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October  9, 2014  2:27PM</date><body>
                     
60% and .00154.No information on one-pay leases from Acura.            </body><username>njacuramdx</username><date>October 10, 2014  4:25AM</date><body>
               Money factor and Residual for 2015 Acura MDX AWD  Advance + Tech and Tech + Ent36 months, 15K miles per year for NJ            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 10, 2014  5:24AM</date><body>
                     
I don't see an Advance + Tech option; Advance + Ent residual is 58% for 36/15.Tech + Ent is 59% for 36/15.MF is .00154 for both.            </body><username>heard006</username><date>October 16, 2014  7:28PM</date><body>
               Hi, I am looking for the MF &amp; Residual for 2015 Acura MDX FWD + Tech.  Washington state and will be 36 months with 12k per year.Thanks!            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 16, 2014 11:29PM</date><body>
                     
.00154 MF and 62% residual            </body><username>sim_sim</username><date>October 18, 2014  3:34AM</date><body>
               Looking for MDX SH-AWD base October numbers for 36/15K in MA. TIA.             </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 18, 2014  1:20PM</date><body>
                     
.00124 MF and 61% residual            </body><username>carshopper116</username><date>October 18, 2014  2:35PM</date><body>
               Hi, am looking at a 2015 Acura MDX with MSRP of 49,725 but after discount and tax tag title doc fee = $48,826. What's the RV and MF for florida? What should it be for a 36/10? 0 down Thank you            </body><username>carshopper116</username><date>October 18, 2014  2:36PM</date><body>
               FWD, tech with entertainment            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 19, 2014 12:37PM</date><body>
                     
36/10 residual is 62%; MF is .00124.With your MSRP and selling price, I get a pre-tax payment of $598.68/mo.            </body><username>rsamerica1</username><date>October 20, 2014  9:56PM</date><body>
               Hello - looking for MF and Residual on 2015 MDX AWD Base and AWD Tech in PA for 36/12 and 36/15 and any known rebates / offers. Thanks.&#160;            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 20, 2014 10:12PM</date><body>
                     
36/15 numbers:AWD Base - 61%AWD Tech - 60%MF is .00124 for both.Add 2% for 12K miles per year.            </body><username>rsamerica1</username><date>October 20, 2014 10:45PM</date><body>
               
Super - thanks.&#160;            </body><username>rsamerica1</username><date>October 22, 2014  8:00PM</date><body>
                     
Super - thanks.&#160;
OK - ready to move on this one - curious as to any comments:2015 MDX AWD BaseMSRP $45,460Cap Cost $42,750Up front $690 (First month payment and standard doc/fees in PA)$550/month payment including 9% taxWith these numbers, appears they are just under invoice, when taking into account the Cap Cost includes $595 acquisition fee (so actual selling price is $42,155, with invoice being $42,163), and up front of $690 minus $550 totals actually less than what the standard title/doc/plate fees are in PA so dealer is absorbing some fees/costs, so feeling pretty good overall.             </body><username>rsamerica1</username><date>October 22, 2014  8:01PM</date><body>
                     
OK - ready to move on this one - curious as to any comments:2015 MDX AWD BaseMSRP $45,460Cap Cost $42,750Up front $690 (First month payment and standard doc/fees in PA)$550/month payment including 9% taxWith these numbers, appears they are just under invoice, when taking into account the Cap Cost includes $595 acquisition fee (so actual selling price is $42,155, with invoice being $42,163), and up front of $690 minus $550 totals actually less than what the standard title/doc/plate fees are in PA so dealer is absorbing some fees/costs, so feeling pretty good overall. To clarify this is 36/15.             </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 22, 2014  8:53PM</date><body>
                     
OK - ready to move on this one - curious as to any comments:2015 MDX AWD BaseMSRP $45,460Cap Cost $42,750Up front $690 (First month payment and standard doc/fees in PA)$550/month payment including 9% taxWith these numbers, appears they are just under invoice, when taking into account the Cap Cost includes $595 acquisition fee (so actual selling price is $42,155, with invoice being $42,163), and up front of $690 minus $550 totals actually less than what the standard title/doc/plate fees are in PA so dealer is absorbing some fees/costs, so feeling pretty good overall. My numbers work out the same as yours ... $550/mo with tax given the prices provided. Only way to lower the payment is to lower the selling price. Might be hard to do on a recently released 2015 model.            </body><username>dublin25</username><date>October 26, 2014  2:12AM</date><body>
               Hello.  I am looking for a 2015 MDX SHAWD with tech package. Wondering what would be a good 36mo 12k lease price with no out of pocket.  In the cincinnati Ohio area.  Thanks.             </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 26, 2014 11:17AM</date><body>
                     
.00111 MF and 62% residual.To calculate a payment, we would need MSRP and selling price.            </body><username>omart007</username><date>October 26, 2014  4:22PM</date><body>
               2015 MDX FWD BaseMSRP $45,460Cap Cost $43,223 - includes $595 acquisition fee$0 down other than title, registation and taxes - first month's payment paid by dealer, $544 (includes tax) due thereafter for 35 months. This is in Miami, FL.  good deal?             </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 26, 2014 10:26PM</date><body>
                     
How many miles per year are allowed?            </body><username>omart007</username><date>October 26, 2014 11:55PM</date><body>
                     
10k             </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 27, 2014 12:35AM</date><body>
                     
.00114 MF and 64% residual for the $0 due at signing lease..  I get $475/mo.+ tax.  So..around $508/mo. including tax?  Maybe they added in a typical for Florida, large dealer fee?            </body><username>willrobinson4</username><date>October 28, 2014  9:14PM</date><body>
               2015 MDX AWD TECH, 12kmiles/36month lease out of CA.  Dealer jerking me around.  Is residual 62% on this vehicle?  I'll assume MF at 0.00124.             </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 28, 2014 10:37PM</date><body>
                     
Your numbers are correct            </body><username>willrobinson4</username><date>October 28, 2014 11:55PM</date><body>
               ^Thanks.  Quoted $600/mo here in CA.  Those numbers yield about $550 w/tax...            </body><username>willrobinson4</username><date>October 29, 2014 12:00AM</date><body>
               ...w/zero-down            </body><username>hmcinc13</username><date>October 30, 2014  2:27AM</date><body>
               36/10k sh awd tech  Msrp 49730.  Cost. 46075 in NYC 1000 down . What my payment should be? What is the mf and residual?             </body><username>vvset</username><date>October 30, 2014  7:44PM</date><body>
               Hello, 36/12k sh awd tech Msrp 49730. Cost. 47000 in MD 0 down . What should a good payment be? What is the mf and residual? One dealer I talked to quoted 665 per month taxes, tile and tags rolled into the payment.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 30, 2014  7:49PM</date><body>
                     
62% and .00124 MF. With your MSRP and selling price, I get a $0 down pre-tax payment of $518.77/mo.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 30, 2014  7:51PM</date><body>
                     
Maryland is one of four states that taxes the entire selling price of the vehicle, making leases very expensive.MF is .00124 and residual is 61% for 36/12. I get a pre-tax $0 down payment of $558.80/mo for 36 months.            </body><username>vvset</username><date>October 30, 2014  8:05PM</date><body>
               Michaell.. Thanks for the prompt response. Much appreciated.. When you say pre tax, are you excluding the sales tax, title and tags expenses..?            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 30, 2014  8:20PM</date><body>
                     
Yes - just using the cost number you provided.            </body><username>ankurg</username><date>October 30, 2014 11:39PM</date><body>
               I am based in NJ. Looking for MDX 2015 AWD with Advance and Entertainment package, 36 months lease and 12K miles per year. what is the current MF and Residual value in NJ ? what is the typical Cap Cost (invoice or somewhat below invoice)?Thanks for your help            </body><username>willrobinson4</username><date>October 30, 2014 11:53PM</date><body>
               Is anyone seeing $550/560 payments here in CA for 36/12/zerodown deals?              </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 31, 2014  1:50AM</date><body>
                     
.00124 MF and 60% residual            </body><username>ankurg</username><date>October 31, 2014  3:36PM</date><body>
               thanks for the reply. What would be your recommendation on starting point for negotiation on this? Invoice price?             </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 31, 2014  5:30PM</date><body>
                     
Use the pricing tools at the top of the page to help ... and, there is an active "MDX Prices Paid" discussion here that might also help you understand what others are paying.            </body><username>bmwfan53</username><date>November  3, 2014  8:45PM</date><body>
               Can you tell me what the Residual and the MF is for an 2014 and 2015 Acura MDX- AWD with Technology &amp; Entertainment package for 36 months at 15K and 39 months at 15K for NJ and TX?            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>November  3, 2014  8:51PM</date><body>
                     
Answered in the other thread.            </body><username>heard006</username><date>November  4, 2014  7:22PM</date><body>
               Hi, I am curious if the MF/RV changed for November in WA state?  I am looking for:  2015 MDX AWD w/Tech 36/12  and also the FWD with Tech 36/12.  Also, if I change to 39/12, does that change the MF &amp; Residual?  Thanks!            </body></posts></thread>