<thread><orig_poster>stever</orig_poster><posted_at_date>November  4, 2014  7:26PM</posted_at_date><posted_at_datetime>2014-07-23T23:39:14+00:00</posted_at_datetime><views>2K</views><replies>49</replies><lastposted_date>July 23, 2014 11:39PM</lastposted_date><lasposted_datetime>2014-11-04T19:26:25+00:00</lasposted_datetime><tags>Acura, Acura RDX, Buying &amp; Selling, Leasing, Values &amp; Prices Paid, 2015</tags><posts><username>stever</username><date>July 23, 2014 11:39PM</date><body>   
               Welcome to the Edmunds discussion dedicated to 2015 Acura RDX leasing questions. 
Here you can find and discuss all the latest lease details for the 2015 RDX, including cap costs, money factors, residual values, acquisition fees, etc. Please post the trim you are shopping, the MSRP, the selling price, any fees and your location (since leases sometimes vary by region).

You can also research local dealer inventory and pricing, reviews, features, and specifications, on our  page.

To see all forums discussions about the Acura RDX, including earlier model years, please visit our list of  discussions.
            </body><username>cesarcoral</username><date>July 23, 2014 11:18PM</date><body>
               Just signed this deal and I hope it is good:

2015 RDX AWD base
36/10,000 miles
$399.00/month
$2794.00 due at signing

Here is the Break Down:
$1,080 Tax
$595 Bank Fee
$399 1st Month payment
$398 Doc Fee
$322 Plates and Reg
$2,794 Total Taxes and Fees.

Selling price: $34,468
            </body><username>cesarcoral</username><date>July 26, 2014  3:04AM</date><body>
               So this the first time I've ever leased and I was shocked when I saw the amount of interest you pay.  I had the formula and for some reason, just concentrated on the money factor of .00160.  That is 3.84%, so I kept thinking that is what I am paying, until I saw the number on the document.  The residual is 63%, so 37,190 * .63 is 23,429.70, the sales price was 34,468, so I'm using 11,038.30 over 36 months. Divide that by 36 and it is 306.62.  The payment is $399.00, so I'm paying $92.38 per month in interest, that is $3,325.70 in interest in 3 years.   A whopping 30%.
            </body><username>cesarcoral</username><date>July 26, 2014  3:22AM</date><body>
               No kidding:

The most common form of leasing seen today is automobile leasing. This is not because leasing a car is cheaper than buying one &#8211; on the contrary, overall it's more expensive. But auto leasing has two principal benefits that make it very popular despite the expense: You can always drive a fairly new car, and it's always under warranty; and, for the same budget, you can often get a larger, more luxurious, better-equipped car.
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>July 26, 2014  1:09PM</date><body>
               You assume you are paying interest on only the depreciation portion of the lease, but that is incorrect.   The bank that you are renting the car from buys it from the dealership.   When they rent it to you, you are basically financing the car over the three years that you have it.   You are borrowing the purchase price (or CAP cost)..   The interest you calculated at 3.84% is correct.   After all, you rented the whole car...   ;-)
            </body><username>cesarcoral</username><date>July 26, 2014  1:46PM</date><body>
               Thanks for the clarification!  You're right, I was assuming I was paying interest on the depreciation only.  I know a lot of people lease but I wonder if people were told they would be paying 30% interest if they would still consider it.  A tight wad like me would wait a little longer to save up more money and buy it out right.  We plan on buying the car if it's as reliable as our past Honda products and would have saved some money just buying it now.  Of course, we would need to come up with $17,000 down to get to $399/month, so I see the benefit of leasing just shocking at first. Live and learn.
            </body><username>stever</username><date>July 26, 2014  2:23PM</date><body>
               I've never leased. Other than some beaters in the early 80s, I'm on my fifth car since '82 and the shortest time I owned one was 10 years.

Talk about boring. 
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>July 26, 2014  2:27PM</date><body>
               

You might be in the wrong discussion..    
            </body><username>stever</username><date>July 26, 2014  2:31PM</date><body>
               I seem to gravitate to discussions where posters like &#8204;  say stuff like "A tight wad like me would wait a little longer to save up more money and buy it out right."

But it's a good chance to remind people who intend to lease that they need to consider the selling price of the car, just like buyers do.
            </body><username>bender63</username><date>August  3, 2014  1:23AM</date><body>
               I am interested in leasing a 2015 rdx awd with tech package for 36 mos. &amp; 15k mi per year.  What is the current residual and mf?  Thanks!
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August  3, 2014  3:06AM</date><body>
               

57% and .00160. $750 lease cash.
            </body><username>anguilla</username><date>August 13, 2014  3:35AM</date><body>
               Can we please reconfirm these numbers from Michaell's August 3rd posting:  57% and .00160. $750 lease cash for the 2015 AWD RDX with Tech package and 15K miles for 3 years?  I only see the $750 lease cash for military veterans, when I do the investigation.  Please advise if all of these numbers still pertain.

Also, please let me know when the these rates will expire and if things typically get better after Labor Day.

Thanks for your advice.
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 13, 2014  5:30AM</date><body>
               

Confirm 57% for RDX AWD with tech for 36/15. Confirm .00160 MF. Lease cash is only available on 2014 MY - my apologies.

Current numbers expire 9/2/14. Magic 8-ball doesn't have any insight as to what will happen after that.
            </body><username>anguilla</username><date>August 13, 2014 10:52AM</date><body>
               Thanks Michaell.  Are these numbers you quote for the 2015, except for the Lease Cash?  Finally, are the residual and money factor numbers consistent anywhere in the US?
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 13, 2014 11:37AM</date><body>
               Those are the 2015 numbers..  Should be nationwide.
            </body><username>nickw44</username><date>August 15, 2014  2:47PM</date><body>
               Hi could I get some numbers on MF/Residual on:

2015 AWD with tech 36m/10K  &amp; 36m/12K
2015 AWD without tech 36m / 10K &amp; 36m / 12K

Any conquest cash?

thanks
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 15, 2014  3:26PM</date><body>
               

with Tech - 62%

w/o Tech - 59%

Add 1% for 10K.

MF is .00160. $750 lease cash.
            </body><username>elvikar</username><date>August 21, 2014  4:58PM</date><body>
               Hi, can i please get number for RDX 2014 AWD without and with tech package, 36 mnths, 10K miles. Any incentives? Plus I have graduated within 2 years from college, can I combine both (if any)? Thnx
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 21, 2014  5:22PM</date><body>
               

RDX AWD - 63%

RDX AWD Tech - 60%

I don't have a MF for the 2014 RDX; assume standard MF of approximately .00200. $750 "inventory payout" for 2014 RDX.

Use the 'car research' tab at the top of the page to link to any other available incentives.
            </body><username>elvikar</username><date>August 21, 2014  6:55PM</date><body>
               

Thank you Michaell!
            </body><username>c300guy</username><date>September 21, 2014 10:12PM</date><body>
               Michaell, what's the current numbers for:2015 AWD RDX with Tech 36 months / 10k miles ?            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 22, 2014 12:32AM</date><body>
                     
MF is .00111 or .00160, depending on state of residence.Residual is 60%            </body><username>c300guy</username><date>September 22, 2014  1:54AM</date><body>
               Thanks.  State is Washington.  Earlier in the thread, it looked like residual was 63%.  (with Tech - 62%w/o Tech - 59%Add 1% for 10K.)            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 22, 2014 11:22AM</date><body>
                     
.00160 MF for WABesides those numbers being swapped (Tech is almost always lower), a new program comes out  just about every month.            </body><username>c300guy</username><date>September 22, 2014  9:25PM</date><body>
               My sales person at the less than reputable Acura dealership just quoted me 57% residual on AWD Tech. package.  Do I tell him to pound sand?  or are these numbers changing frequently?            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 22, 2014 11:23PM</date><body>
                     
2015 Acura RDX AWD w/Tech is 57% residual for 36mo, 15K/yr.    60% for 36mo, 10K/yr.Dealers can't change residuals.   They won't be able to write a lease with any other number.            </body><username>c300guy</username><date>September 25, 2014  5:05AM</date><body>
               Went to the other Acura dealership in town.  Called\emailed them first.  They quoted me 63% residual on AWD Tech RDX, and .00154 MF.  I said that didn't sound right, they claimed the numbers were right from Acura, i expressed my feelings again that this wasn't right, as per the other dealership and Edmunds.  They claimed it was truth and gave me final numbers.  I went down there, they said "oops, we had the numbers wrong, here are the right numbers".Word to the list - the numbers on this board reflect reality, i really appreciate the moderators that post them here.  don't let a dealer tell you otherwise!            </body><username>eurocarlov1</username><date>October  4, 2014  3:19AM</date><body>
               Hi all.  Can someone please provide October residual and MF for 2015 RDX AWD w/ Tech?  Thanks very much!             </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October  4, 2014  1:15PM</date><body>
                     
.00111 or .00160 MF, depending on state.  57% residual for 36mo, 15K/yr            </body><username>anguilla</username><date>October  6, 2014 12:42PM</date><body>
               Looking for a  2015 RDX AWD with Tech package.  36 month lease with 15k/year.There are a few dealers in nearby states that have good discounts off of MSRP.  What is the money factor and residual in each of these states for October and how long are these rates typically valid for?NJMDVAPANY            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October  6, 2014  1:19PM</date><body>
                     
Answered in the other thread.            </body><username>cbarsh</username><date>October 15, 2014  2:22PM</date><body>
               Looking for a base model front wheel drive. How good are the two factory offers? $430month $0 drive off and $379 month $1999 drive off. How much better can expect to do with So Cal dealers? Or go with one of these offers?            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 15, 2014  2:48PM</date><body>
                     
Not enough information ... we need to know the MSRP, negotiated selling price and the lease term / miles per year.36/15 residual for base FWD is 60% and the base MF is .00111.            </body><username>pionero</username><date>October 16, 2014  1:01AM</date><body>
               Hello. Looking at 2015 RDX w/ FWD, no tech package. Only paying tax, title, license upfront on 36 month/10k lease. Two places I contacted in NJ initially offered $400/month. I feel this is much too high. What's the lowest price per month I can try to get?  Thank you.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 16, 2014 11:33AM</date><body>
                     
Hard to say .. we would need to know the MSRP and selling price in order to model a payment.MF is .00111 and 36/10 residual is 63% for FWD Base.            </body><username>pionero</username><date>October 17, 2014 12:04AM</date><body>
               
MSRP $35,990. Selling 34,995.&#160;Thanks.&#160;            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 17, 2014  8:04PM</date><body>
                     
MSRP $35,990. Selling 34,995.&#160;Thanks.&#160;
With your MSRP and selling price, I get a pre-tax payment of $406.27/mo for 36 months. Your offer looks pretty strong.            </body><username>jlr434</username><date>October 20, 2014  7:45PM</date><body>
               I'm looking for the October MF &amp; RV for a 2015 Acura RDX with Tech Pkg. for the state of Illinois.  Are their conquest dollars available?  And, any idea what November numbers might be?  Thank you!            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 20, 2014 10:02PM</date><body>
                     
What lease term and miles per year?Leasing in Illinois will be very expensive as the entire purchase price is subject to sales tax. That law is changing on 1/1/15.No idea what the numbers for November will look like.            </body><username>jlr434</username><date>October 21, 2014  5:53PM</date><body>
               Sorry I didn't include lease terms.....36 mo/15 K.  We've been leasing cars for 20 years.  So grateful to have these leasing forums now. This information is invaluable!I heard leasing rules were changing for Il in 2015.  Current lease on Acura TL ends 11/3/14 so trying to figure out if we should lease now or try and wait til 1/15.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 21, 2014  7:29PM</date><body>
                     
If you can wait, I would recommend it. As of 1/1/15, only the monthly payment will be subject to sales tax, not the entire purchase amount of the vehicle. Should bring down the payment by $40-50 a month, give or take.RDX SH-AWD Tech residual is 57% for 36/15. MF is .00111.            </body><username>bobsparrow</username><date>October 23, 2014  6:25PM</date><body>
               Hi!Looking for the MF and Residual on a 2015 RDX AWD with Tech Package36/12K NYThanks in advance!            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 23, 2014  6:43PM</date><body>
                     
RDX AWD Tech - 62% and .00111            </body><username>straightdope</username><date>October 24, 2014  7:25PM</date><body>
               HEY-SHOP AROUND YOU CAN BEAT THE NATIONAL $430, $0 DRIVE OFF LEASE OFFER ON A 2015 ACURA RDX BASE.  Every Southern Calif dealer I contacted beat it upon asking, but the price varied considerably, and the best was $390/month with 0 due at signing. Here is my October deal with an LA area which was matched by two other dealers (in Ventura Cty, other in Orange Cty). RDX Base MSRP $35,990PRICE: $33,836RV: $22673MF.00111Net CapCost: 34431 ((Acq Fee $595) Dealer paid DMV fees &amp; first payment of 900)Payments: $390/month + sales tax for 36 months, 10k miles year. $0 Drive offs, $0 cash out of pocket at signing, so 35 payments x 390 = $13,650  total cost plus $350 lease end/disposition fee. Hope this helps.            </body><username>overthis</username><date>October 30, 2014  7:37PM</date><body>
               Looking at a lease on a 2015 Acura RDX AWD w/Nav MSRP 40,890.  Being quoted $3k down $478 per month including tax PA(9%). Spec sheet has acquisition at $595 and $289.55 in fees.  They are pushing due to end of month...I am in no hurry  Thoughts?            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 30, 2014  7:41PM</date><body>
                     
What is the selling price? Lease term and miles per year?How much (if any) of the $3K due at signing is for cap cost reduction?            </body><username>overthis</username><date>October 30, 2014  8:11PM</date><body>
                     
Selling price 38,892 36 month 12k/miles $2048.50 cap reduction            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October 30, 2014  8:25PM</date><body>
                     
First, we don't recommend any sort of cap reduction on a lease ... if the car is stolen or totaled, you are out that money.Does this car have the tech package? I have two residuals for the RDX AWD - 62% for base and 59% for tech.MF is .00111. Using the 59% residual, I get a pre-tax payment of $480.14/mo for 36 months. 9% tax takes the payment of $523.35/mo.Down payment saves you approximately $28/mo for every $1000 down.            </body><username>overthis</username><date>October 30, 2014  8:38PM</date><body>
                     
It is tech package and they are using 59% residual and .00111 MF.  I do not usually put money down on a lease either.  Seems like I can do a little better. Thanks!            </body><username>heard006</username><date>November  4, 2014  7:26PM</date><body>
                I am looking for:  2015 RDX AWD w/Tech 36/10  and also the FWD with Tech 36/12 for Washington state.  Also, if I change to 39/10, does that change the MF &amp; Residual?  Thanks!            </body></posts></thread>