<thread><orig_poster>jessesj</orig_poster><posted_at_date>November  4, 2014  5:02PM</posted_at_date><posted_at_datetime>2014-08-05T20:05:32+00:00</posted_at_datetime><views>6.1K</views><replies>63</replies><lastposted_date>August  5, 2014  8:05PM</lastposted_date><lasposted_datetime>2014-11-04T17:02:39+00:00</lasposted_datetime><tags>Acura, Buying &amp; Selling, Leasing, 2015, Acura TLX</tags><posts><username>jessesj</username><date>August  5, 2014  8:05PM</date><body>   
               Looking for any information on Acura's current lease program on the new TLX model.  Specifically, money factor &amp; residual value for the 4-cyl. w/ tech package would be most helpful.  Assuming 36 mos., 15k miles per year.  Thanks in advance.
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August  5, 2014 10:45PM</date><body>
               

.00135 MF and 60% residual
            </body><username>jessesj</username><date>August  7, 2014 12:03PM</date><body>
               Thanks again. Would you please provide the same figures for the 4-cyl. base model assuming 36 mos./15k miles?
            </body><username>dmgoodman</username><date>August  7, 2014  3:33PM</date><body>
               Need to get MF and residual for Acura TLX - 4 cylinder with Tech Package.  10k and 12k miles, 36 month lease. Thanks in advance for your help. I am in Arizona.
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August  7, 2014 10:13PM</date><body>
               

.00135 MF and 63% residual
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August  7, 2014 10:13PM</date><body>
               

.00135 MF and 63%/62% residual.
            </body><username>dmgoodman</username><date>August  8, 2014 12:56AM</date><body>
               Thank you, kyfdx.            </body><username>heischjr</username><date>August  8, 2014 12:23PM</date><body>
               Do the residual and money factor change for the 4 cylinder base for 36 months and 12k miles or are they the same as above for the tech?
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August  9, 2014 12:41AM</date><body>
               

.00135 MF and 65% residual for base.
            </body><username>kencpo</username><date>August 10, 2014 11:14AM</date><body>
               I am coming off a TSX lease.  The TLX will be 369 plus tax for 0 down 36 mo with 10k a year.  That is based on MSRP.  Dealer said no one is discounting MSRP.  Any info on this or on the dealer's invoice. Base 4 cyl model
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 10, 2014  5:29PM</date><body>
               

If Edmunds has the invoice prices for this model, you can find them by using the tabs at the top of the page.    One dealer only knows what they are doing.  I would surely not accept what they say at face value, without shopping around.

.00135 MF and 66% residual for that model and term/mileage.
            </body><username>stgeorge78</username><date>August 14, 2014 12:49AM</date><body>
               Any info on MF/Residual for 2015 TLX with SH-AWD Tech package? 10k miles and 36 months.
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 14, 2014  3:09AM</date><body>
               

.00135 MF and 60% residual
            </body><username>lurker315</username><date>August 23, 2014  2:35AM</date><body>
               Would like to lease a 2015 TLX P-AWS Advanced for 36 mo/15k miles

What is the MF and residual?
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 23, 2014  2:12PM</date><body>
               

.00123 MF and 55% residual
            </body><username>yescar</username><date>August 23, 2014  6:36PM</date><body>
               Interested in a TLX 3.5 P-AWS with Technology package.  Anyone know the MF and 3 year residual with 36 month lease, 15K miles/year?
In addition, has anyone found a dealer that is willing to sell for less than MSRP?
I wonder if they'll be more willing to negotiate after the car's been out for a few months?
Thanks in advance
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 24, 2014  3:50AM</date><body>
               

TLX V6 AWD with Tech ... 57% and .00123

All you can do is present your offer that is under MSRP and see if the dealer accepts.
            </body><username>kermitdog</username><date>August 24, 2014  1:13PM</date><body>
               Can you please post the MF and residual for 2015 TLX 3.5V6 front wheel drive with Technology package?  36 months, 15K miles per year.  Also, is there any difference in the residual for the Advance package?  Thank you.
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 24, 2014  1:53PM</date><body>
               

TLX V6 with Tech - 59%

Deduct 2% for the Advance package.

.00123 MF for both.
            </body><username>zaffy</username><date>August 29, 2014  6:16AM</date><body>
               Could you post up MF and RVs for TLX V6 base and Tech vs TLX I-4 base and Tech. FWD for both 12k @ 36mo Thanks!
            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>August 29, 2014 11:33AM</date><body>
               

.00135 MF for I-4
.00123 MF for V-6

65% residual for I-4
62% residual w/Tech

64% residual for V-6
61% residual w/Tech
            </body><username>jd99</username><date>August 30, 2014  1:32AM</date><body>
               Has anyone received a good lease on the base 4 cylinder tlx
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>August 31, 2014  4:15AM</date><body>
               

Use the quoted MF above and plug in the MSRP and negotiated selling price into any good lease calculator to determine your target payment.
            </body><username>yescar</username><date>September  1, 2014  4:08PM</date><body>
               

Interested in this myself.  I've contacted a few dealers, and they don't want to discount much off of MSRP.  I guess because the model is so new.  Guess I'll have to check out some other options or wait a while.
            </body><username>heischjr</username><date>September  2, 2014  3:02PM</date><body>
               

Best price I've gotten is $399/mo. including taxes with $0 down for 36 months and 12k miles per year.  Base V-6 I received a quote for $439 with $0 down. 
Anyone received anything better?
            </body><username>epc949</username><date>September  2, 2014  7:44PM</date><body>
               Where did you get this offer?  I'm in Arizona and the best I can get for the 4 cyl. With tech package is 379/mo. with 2500.00 and 10k a year.            </body><username>heischjr</username><date>September  2, 2014  8:22PM</date><body>
               I'm in Ohio so we probably have more inventory than most states.
            </body><username>yescar</username><date>September  2, 2014 10:49PM</date><body>
               I've now started to get a little more willingness to negotiate.  Nothing great though.  I guess Acura doesn't want to start discounting such a new model.  I'd like to get this car, but not going to pay a premium.  All kinds of deals on BMW 3 series, Infiniti Q50's, etc&#8230;..
            </body><username>yescar</username><date>September  6, 2014  8:21PM</date><body>
               Would appreciate the September Residuals and MF on a 36 month/15 K miles lease on the following. 1)V-6 P-AWS with Technology package, and 2) V-6 AWD with Tech package.   Thanks in advance
            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September  7, 2014  1:02PM</date><body>
               

1)V-6 P-AWS with Technology package

59%

2) V-6 AWD with Tech package.   Thanks in advance

57%

.00123 MF for both
            </body><username>cb4d1</username><date>September 12, 2014  5:16PM</date><body>
               Could I get numbers on base 4cyl in CA, 3 year @ 12k/year? Thanks in advance.             </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September 12, 2014  5:55PM</date><body>
                     
65% residual and .00135 MF            </body><username>mehtaa24</username><date>September 13, 2014 11:30AM</date><body>
               In NJ here, best price I got was $399 after taxes, including $7000 trade in. No deal...dealer wouldnt tell me MF and residual. can I get numbers on V-6 Tech and V-6 Advanced            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 13, 2014 12:19PM</date><body>
                     
.00123 MF for all V-6 models.Residuals for 59% for Tech, 57% for Advance for 36mo, 15K/yr.Subtract 2% for AWD            </body><username>crni123</username><date>September 13, 2014  9:40PM</date><body>
               Ok can't find any dealer to sell less than sticker. Might just wait 4 months till they start neg. Does anyone know if they do MSD to lower interest rate. What also is current money factor and residual for a v6 tech fwd. 36/12. Or 15. Thank you&#160;            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September 14, 2014  4:52AM</date><body>
                     
.00123 MF for all V-6 models.Residuals for 59% for Tech for 36/15. Add 2% for 12K.Not certain that Acura does an MSD program.            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>September 14, 2014  2:09PM</date><body>
               No MSD program for Acura            </body><username>whodunits</username><date>September 23, 2014  5:08AM</date><body>
               Please advise MF/Residuals for 2015 TLX V-6 SH-AWD Advance package? 7500 and 10k miles, 24, 27 and 36 months.  Thank you.            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>September 23, 2014 12:55PM</date><body>
                     
24/10 - 64%27/10 - 63%36/10 - 58%.00123 MF for all terms.No 7500 mile numbers available, but generally add 1% to RV from 10K.            </body><username>mushtar</username><date>October  2, 2014 10:15PM</date><body>
               Any numbers for October for TLX 2.4 w/ Tech, 36k @ 10k?            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October  3, 2014 12:07AM</date><body>
                     
.00135 MF and 63% residual            </body><username>mushtar</username><date>October  3, 2014 12:20AM</date><body>
               Thanks!            </body><username>hillestadk</username><date>October  3, 2014  1:37PM</date><body>
               Helping a friend out with a lease.  Just wondering the mf and residual on a 15 TLX base model 36/15.  Thanks in advance! you guys are so helpful            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October  3, 2014  1:47PM</date><body>
                     
63% and .00135 for 4-cyl62% and .00123 for V6            </body><username>dreamspeed</username><date>October  5, 2014  5:27PM</date><body>
               Can I please get the MF and residuals for 2015 4-cyl base and tech package for 12/36 and 10/36? Thanks            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October  5, 2014  9:38PM</date><body>
                     
.00135 MFBase:  65%/66% residualTech:  62%/63% residual            </body><username>therival</username><date>October  8, 2014  3:42PM</date><body>
               looking for MF and Residual on a 2015 TLX SH-AWD tech in upstate ny 10/36 and 12/36            </body><username>Michaell</username><date>October  8, 2014  5:42PM</date><body>
                     
59% for 36/12. Add 1% for 10K..00123 MF for all V6's.            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 23, 2014  2:27AM</date><body>
               I got a base 4cyl TLX for $380/mth, 10k miles, 36 months.  Did I do ok?  Never leased before, so it was a learning experience.  That's with nasty Cook (Crook!!) county IL tax, and no trade.  I think IL is the only state that charges tax on the full price on the car, rather than the leased portion.   thanks            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 23, 2014  2:30AM</date><body>
               Oh, that with no money down.  Forgot to mention....            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 23, 2014  3:22AM</date><body>
                     
For Illinois, it doesn't sound too bad.  What is the MSRP?Quite a few states charge full tax on the selling price.   GA, MD and TX are a few of the others...            </body><username>fritz21</username><date>October 23, 2014  3:32AM</date><body>
               I was quoted 365 for a tlx base tonight 36/12.30,899 selling price and 20,728 residual with 2,000 down. 6.5% sales tax. FYI            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 23, 2014  3:34AM</date><body>
               Total price: 30,881 per the state tax form.  I think Cook County IL tax is 8.25%.  thanks            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 23, 2014  3:36AM</date><body>
               Guess my residual is $21,047.40  I got silver BTW.  I normally get the Graphite color, but seems really dark on the TLX.            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 23, 2014  3:42AM</date><body>
               I also will get hit with a $350 turn in fee, if I don't buy the car at end of lease.  I don't know if that is standard, but I probably would have tried to negotiate it if I had know.  It was never mentioned until I was signing all the docs.            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 23, 2014 11:19AM</date><body>
                     
Almost every lease has a disposition fee.  It's pretty standard and charged by the bank, not the dealer.   You can't negotiate that away.   Most captive banks waive the fee, if you lease another car of the same make at lease end.            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 24, 2014  2:58AM</date><body>
               Thanks for the info.  Still had I known, I would probably stuck to my original target of $374/month, and I think I would have gotten it.            </body><username>itztico</username><date>October 29, 2014  1:32AM</date><body>
               hi everyone. im going to the dealer on saturday and want to get as much information as possible to get the best deal for the tlx. does the MF and RV change in November, if so, are the numbers out? I'm interested in knowing for the following. V6 12K miles/36 months 0 down just pay taxesV6 TECH 12K miles/36 months 0 down just pay taxesthank you for all help.             </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 29, 2014  3:06AM</date><body>
                     
Current Acura numbers run through November 3rd..00123 MF and 64% residual for the base V6 model.   61% residual for the V6 Tech model.            </body><username>mm7</username><date>October 29, 2014  3:25AM</date><body>
               So are the money factor and residuals pretty much set in stone each month, leaving only the purchase price negotiable?            </body><username>kyfdx</username><date>October 29, 2014 11:10AM</date><body>
                     
Yes...  In theory, dealers can mark up the money factor for extra profit, but Acura dealers rarely do that.And, as in any auto transaction, watch out for extra charges and maintenance/insurance plans that you don't need.            </body><username>snaider</username><date>November  2, 2014 11:25PM</date><body>
               Hi,I'm starting my research and am looking for the November Residual and MF for V6 SH-AWD with Advance Package. 15K/year Thanks in Advance             </body><username>Michaell</username><date>November  3, 2014  1:49AM</date><body>
                     
Acura numbers expire tomorrow: 55% for 36/15 and .00123 MF.November numbers should be available later this week.            </body><username>jarbl</username><date>November  4, 2014  5:02PM</date><body>
               I'm looking for residual and MF on the 4 and 6 cylinder base for 36 months-15k/year            </body></posts></thread>